TYLER MOWBRAY

PRODUCTION ASSISTANT

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS:

A creative communications leader with more than 5 years experience driving communication and leadership in a team environment. Strong ability to prioritize tasks, work well with others, and excel individually under pressure. Proficient in MS Office, Avid, HTML, Microsoft CRM, and Archtics.

RELATED MEDIA EXPERIENCE:

COLUMBUS SPORTS NETWORK

AUG. **2007** – FEB. **2008**

TV Production Intern

- Assisted in the production and setup for all Columbus Sports Network events including: Major League Soccer, Arena Football League, Minor League Baseball, and High School Football.
- Edited, cut, and logged game films for "Sports Columbus" highlight packages, a nightly 30-minute live broadcast.
- Coordinated Score Bug graphics for remote events.
- Operated Parabolic Microphone.
- Wrote Press releases on upcoming CSN events.

CAPITAL UNIVERSITY MAY 2006- JULY 2009

Skyline Columbus

- Contributed in the production and setup of Skyline Columbus, a 1-hour live university program.
- Gained beneficial experience in all aspect of production; Lighting, audio, editing (Avid, Final Cut), directing, and working the switchboard.

CAPITAL UNIVERSITY MAY 2006- JULY 2009

WXCU Radio

- DJ for WXCU Radio. CMJ Award winner for Best Student-Run Internet Station.
- Hosted live University programming including a 30-minute sports talk show.
- Created radio sweeps.

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

COLUMBUS CREW MARCH 2014 - SEPT. 2014

Account Executive

Developed new business via cold calls, B2B, networking events, and youth soccer tournaments.

NATIONAL COLLEGIATE SCOUTING ASSOCIATION

MAY 2013 - DEC. 2013

Account Executive

 Evaluated student-athlete's academic and athletic abilities, while effectively communicating the importance of NCSA's role in the recruiting process.

CHICAGO FIRE SOCCER CLUB

JULY **2011 - APRIL 2013**

Account Executive

- Increased season ticket base and helped grow total attendance by 15% from 2011 to 2012.
- Facilitated fundraising campaigns for youth soccer clubs and business in the Chicagoland area.

CHICAGO FIRE SOCCER CLUB

MAY 2011- JULY 2011

Inside Sales Representative

- Focused on growing season ticket base via outbound call campaign, exceeding 100 calls daily.
- Led Inside Sales class in revenue and sales, being promoted 3 months into an 8-month program.

TAMPA BAY RAYS JAN 2010 - JUNE 2010

Sales and Service Intern

Provided superior Ticket Sales & Service to 600 Tampa Bay Rays season ticket holders.

EDUCATION:

CAPITAL UNIVERSITY, COLUMBUS, OH

Bachelor of Arts - 2009

Radio/Television/Film, Communications

CAPITAL UNIVERSITY SOCCER MEN'S SOCCER

4 Year Starter • 2 Year Captain ('08, '09) • 2 Time Ohio Athletic Conference Champions